Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Photograph Collection
1850s-2000s
New York University Archives
New York University
PHOTO.00001
478 Linear Feet in 478 boxes
Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Aerial photographs.; New York University -- Buildings.; Photographs.
- Washington Square Park
  Scope and Content Note
  This series contains photographs and prints of Washington Square Park as well as the structures surrounding the four sides of the Park.
  - Subseries A: Aerial Views
    - Aerial Views, 1890s, 1890-1899, 2001, undated (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1907; wsp_av_1_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, circa 1890; wsp_av_1_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 2)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1890; wsp_av_1_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Aerial Views, 1900-1919 (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1919; wsp_av_1_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Aerial Views, 1920s, 1920-1929 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1926; wsp_av_1_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1913; wsp_av_1_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1920; wsp_av_1_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, circa 1926; wsp_av_1_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1926; wsp_av_1_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1926; wsp_av_1_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, 1926; wsp_av_1_3_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, 1926; wsp_av_1_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Aerial Views, 1930s, 1930-1939 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1930-1939; wsp_av_1_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1934; wsp_av_1_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1939; wsp_av_1_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1930-1939; wsp_av_1_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1937; wsp_av_1_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Aerial Views, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, circa 1940-1949; wsp_av_1_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1947; wsp_av_1_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1940-1949; wsp_av_1_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1940; wsp_av_1_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 4)
        Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1943; wsp_av_1_5_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area, Aerial View, 1947; wsp_av_1_5_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 6)
        Aerial photographs.
    - Aerial Views, 1946-50, 1946-1950 (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946; wsp_av_1_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 1)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1947; wsp_av_1_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, 1949; wsp_av_1_6_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946; wsp_av_1_6_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_6_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1949; wsp_av_1_6_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 12)
    - Aerial Views, 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_av_1_7_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Winter Scene, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950-1959; wsp_av_1_7_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Winter Scene, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_7_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_av_1_7_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950-1959; wsp_av_1_7_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1954; wsp_av_1_7_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1959; wsp_av_1_7_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_av_1_7_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1954; wsp_av_1_7_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1954; wsp_av_1_7_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 14)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 15)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 16)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 17)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 18)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_7_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 19)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_7_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 20)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 21)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 22)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, 1951; wsp_av_1_7_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 23)
    - Aerial Views, 1960s (Folder 1 of 2), 1960-1969 (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960; wsp_av_1_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1965; wsp_av_1_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Cars, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area, Aerial View, Looking South, 1964; wsp_av_1_8_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1965; wsp_av_1_8_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_1_8_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1963; wsp_av_1_8_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1964; wsp_av_1_8_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 14)
    - Aerial Views, 1960s (Folder 2 of 2), 1960-1969 (Box 207, Folder 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1969; wsp_av_2_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_av_2_1_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1969; wsp_av_2_1_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1964; wsp_av_2_1_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960's; wsp_av_2_1_11 (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_1_12 (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - New York University Buildings, Washington Square Area, Aerial View, 1967; wsp_av_2_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 13)
        Aerial photographs.; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 14)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, 1963; wsp_av_2_1_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 15)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 16)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Aerial photographs.
      - Washington Square Park, Looking Southwest, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_17; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 17)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_18; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 18)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_19; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 19)
      - Washington Square Arch, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_20; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 20)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_21; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 21)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 22)
        New York (N.Y.).; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 23)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_av_2_1_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 24)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1965; wsp_av_2_1_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - Aerial Views, 1965 Shadow Study (Box 207, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_02 (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Aerial Views, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking Southwest, 1970; wsp_av_2_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, 1979; wsp_av_2_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1971; wsp_av_2_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1971; wsp_av_2_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1970-1979; wsp_av_2_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1971; wsp_av_2_3_07; color print(photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1970-1979; wsp_av_2_3_08 (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1971; wsp_av_2_3_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1971; wsp_av_2_3_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1970; wsp_av_2_3_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 11)
        Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Aerial photographs.; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1972; wsp_av_2_3_12; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_3_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1975; wsp_av_2_3_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1970-1979; wsp_av_2_3_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - Aerial Views, North - Undated (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Aerial Views, South - Undated (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, undated; wsp_av_2_5_01; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, undated; wsp_av_2_5_02; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Crowd in Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Aerial Views, East - Undated (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Aerial Views, West - Undated (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Aerial Views, Undated (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - NYU Commencement in Washington Square Park, Aerial View from Judson Tower, circa 1970-1979; wsp_av_2_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 8, Item 1)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Student activities.
      - Washington Square Arch and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, undated; wsp_av_2_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 207, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Arch and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, undated; wsp_av_2_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - NYU Commencement in Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_8_04; color postcard, 7 x 8 inches (Box 207, Folder 8, Item 4)
        Aerial photographs.; Student activities.; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, undated; wsp_av_2_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_8_06 (Box 207, Folder 8, Item 6)